Finding Aid for Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County records, 1980-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County records 1980-1992
Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County.
1 linear foot
2010139 Ba 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group came from the organization through the Rev. Terry N. Smith (donor no. 10389 ) in June 2010.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County is a coalition of congregations and mental health service agencies. Its mission is to "work together to improve the quality of life of people in our community, particularly those who suffer from mental illness, developmental disabilities or personal crisis -- as well as to promote good mental health for all persons." The organization was established in 1980.
The records of Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County have been arranged into a single organizational files series. The series dates from 1980 to 1992 and includes files relating to the mission and administration of the organization. Of greatest value are the minutes of the annual meetings and of the steering committee. Other files relate to specific activities, such as workshops and conferences on the issue of treating mental illness.
Subjects:
Interdenominational cooperation--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Parish Partnerships of Washtenaw County.; People with mental disabilities--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Washtenaw County (Mich.)
- Organizational records, 1980-1992
  - Annual Meetings, Minutes
    - 1984 (Box 1)
    - 1989 (Box 1)
    - 1990 (Box 1)
  - Awards: William A. Lutz Award (Box 1)
  - Brochures, handouts (Box 1)
  - Conference, Quality of Life (Box 1)
  - Correspondence
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - 1990 Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - 1990: Pathways to Partnerships: An Awareness & Resource Guide to M.I., Response & Letters (Box 1)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Financial
    - Finance Committee Minutes (Box 1)
    - James, Muriel (Box 1)
    - Treasurers Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - Fundraising, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Future Selves
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Minutes (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Lectureships
    - Bradshaw, John (Box 1)
    - James, Muriel
      - General, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - National Employees Health & Fitness Day (NEH & FD) (Box 1)
    - Peck, Scott (Box 1)
    - Siegel, Bernie
      - General (Box 1)
      - Evaluation Results (Box 1)
      - Mailing List (Box 1)
    - Wilson-Shaef, Ann (Box 1)
  - Mailing Information
    - Faith in Action (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Parish Partnerships
      - Church (Box 1)
      - Steering Committing (Box 1)
    - Pathways to Promises Booklets, Requests (Box 1)
  - Meeting Minutes
    - Executive, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Public Education Committee (Box 1)
    - Steering Committee, 1980-1992, 6 folders (Box 1)
  - Mental Health Awareness Month
    - General, October 1990 (Box 1)
    - Advertising Madhatters (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor Area Foundation (Box 1)
    - Madhatters (Box 1)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 1)
  - Ministries
    - Adult Foster Care, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Community Housing Coalition (Box 1)
    - Spring Ministry Day, 1985 (Box 1)
    - St. Andrews (Box 1)
    - Workshop (Box 1)
  - Program Information
    - By-Laws (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Mission Statement (Box 1)
    - Survey of Churches, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Survey of Churches of Downtown Ypsilanti (Box 1)
    - Time Survey (Box 1)
    - Videotape (papers about informative videotape) (Box 1)